Grandma, why are you here
奶奶你怎么过来了
Hey
哎
Miss Chiang
蒋小姐
Why are you here, too
你怎么也在这里啊
Come on, everybody raise your glasses
来来大家举杯
Is that Mr. Tsui Chin-feng
是徐津枫先生吗
Please come with us
麻烦跟我们走一趟
Grandma, grandma
奶奶奶奶
Send to hospital
送医院
Grandma
奶奶
I don't want to see her
我不想见她
Don't call me Grandma
别叫我奶奶
I brought you up by myself
我一个人把你拉扯大
You joined a girl film to lie to me
你竟然联合一个丫头片子来骗我
There will be a board meeting soon
马上要开董事大会了
How many people are staring at you in the back
后边有多少人盯着你呢
You still have the heart to do that
你还有心思搞那事
As you know, the shareholders' meeting will be held soon
你也知道马上要开股东大会了
Then you arranged for my blind date to go to England
那你还把我相亲安排到英国去了呢
That's different
那可不一样
I will never allow a person who lies to me to enter my house
我绝对不允许一个骗我的人进我家门
I already told her at home
我已经告诉她家里了
I told them to know how they educate their children
我叫他们知道他们怎么教育的孩子
Grandma
奶奶
Grandma is still angry
奶奶还在气头上
Just wait for her anger to subside
等她气消了就好了
You know
你知道
How much does it cost to raise a child
养大一个孩子要花多少钱吗
My mother brought me up alone
我妈是一个人把我带大
I can spend all my money on me
在我身上能花光了所有的钱
But now she's
但她现在
Because I'm selfish
竟然因为我自私的
Touched the world that doesn't belong to me
触碰了不属于我的世界
And blame yourself for not saving some worthy dowry
而责怪自己没有攒下些配得上的嫁妆
So that I won't be looked down upon by your family
好让我不要被你们家瞧不起
How could I feel unworthy
我怎么会觉得不配
We
我们
Split up
分开吧
I'm sorry, Yulu
对不起啊玉露
We didn't know you and
我们之前不知道你和
I also told you about him and Director Chen
还跟你说他和陈总监的事
It's okay. It's all over
没事都过去了
Thank you for taking care of me during this time
谢谢这段时间大家对我的照顾
We will be competitors in the future
以后我们就是竞争对手了
You have to cheer up
你们要加油啊
Ms. Qing Lin Yulu changed jobs with high salary
庆 林玉露女士高薪跳槽
Grandma's meaning is very firm
奶奶的意思很坚决
Before you and Miss Chen get married
在你和陈小姐结婚之前
She won't let you out
她是不会放你出去了
How is she
她怎么样
Leave one's job
离职了
Her work plan is still in the company's encrypted data
她的工作方案还在公司加密资料里
These are all her painstaking efforts
这些都是她的心血
It should belong to her
理应属于她
How about this
这样吧
You sign this
你在这上面签个字
I'll help you settle all this down
我帮你安顿好这一切
Thank you, brother
谢谢哥
Should
应该的
This one has excellent academic performance since childhood
这个从小品学兼优
Master of Tsinghua
清华硕士
Beijing Hukou
北京户口
COE of Dachang
大厂的COE
Have a house and a car
有房有车
Excuse me, are you Lin
请问您是林
Miss Lin
林小姐吗
Excuse me, are you Miss Lin
请问 您是林小姐吗
The weather is not bad
天气还不错
I didn't expect us to be fellow villagers
没想到我们还是老乡
I'm going to buy another house in my hometown in the past two years
这两年我准备在老家再买一套房子
If we are destined to be together,
如果我们有缘能在一起的话
You can also settle your parents together
也可以一起安顿父母